Hello
[Music]
Hello friends Anand Saraswat Nibha Health
Insurance Advisor welcomes you to your channel
Prince
don't forget to like subscribe and share the channel and you
need a reminder for important meetings below but there is no limit given you
can take a room on rent this is very important to pay attention to
and many
points are
referred to and according to that hospital
expenses are also calculated so friends
while taking a hospital it is very important to keep that in mind if you have taken a house
and you are
in a room then suppose
if you are getting admitted for tens then your
total expense will be 10
and the remaining time which is left of flat
2012 rupees only that will be left for you
for treatment so friends the
point of room rent concept should be
well in our mind
whenever we are going to take any plan
God why did you not think before that if you take a
room of 10000 then it costs up
to one lakh rupees on room
rent  The mole in the stomach is gone, now
only 1 lakh is left, if
someone else gets admitted in the whole year then how will we
cover the expenses, you should have thought about this earlier, I will pay for 10,000,
brother, whenever there is hospitalization,
both the room expenses and constipation are
kept in mind
[Music]